<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Golov's blog</title>
        <description>Golov's blog - Peter Golov</description>
        <link>http://golov.me</link>
        <link>http://golov.me</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2014-02-26T13:03:11+04:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2014-02-26T13:03:11+04:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Hello World!</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog will be about the things that interest me, and what I feel I can share with the world. Being a programmer, it will mostly be tech things, as that is what I spend most of my precious time on. I mostly develop in Ruby and Javascript, as well as dev ops with Puppet. So there might be some of that. There might also be some bad jokes, I can’t always help myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been contracting for a couple of years (I’m available, get in touch!), but recently, I decided to start some product development. Instead of making task manager or blogging system (I don’t know what I was thinking), I decided to make something I’ve always wanted to - a game. Solo-development can get lonely, so I want to share some of my design decisions, struggles and triumphs with the blogosphere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It so happens, that I started this game development concurrently with another major life event - moving to Russia. I am a Russian national, but my family moved westwards when I was 7, just over 20 years ago. We lived in Germany, Japan, Canada and for the last 14 years in the UK. While I will always feel Russian, I very much have western cultural values. I will try to write about the particularly interesting Russian experiences. My wife is also writing a &lt;a href=&quot;http://hellomoskva.com&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt; about some of the things we’ve encountered, and just a guide about how and what to do in Moscow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
                <link>http://golov.me/2014/02/25/new-post</link>
                <guid>http://golov.me/2014/02/25/new-post</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-02-25T00:00:00+04:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
